[{"answer": "Give me this fucking thing", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "I'm sick of fuckin hearin it my friend, I'll give it back when we leave", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What the fuck do you think you're doin?  Give me my book back", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Whaddaya mean, give it to me when we leave, give it back now", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Have you guys been listening to ", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Can you believe the songs they been playin", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "C'mon, throw in a buck", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Whaddaya mean you don't tip", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "U", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I don't believe in it", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Whaddaya mean you don't tip", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You don't believe in tipping", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't tip because society says I gotta.  I tip when somebody deserves a tip.  When somebody really puts forth an effort, they deserve a little something extra. But this tipping automatically, that shit's for the birds.  As far as I'm concerned, they're just doin their job", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Our girl was okay.  She didn't do anything special", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Okay ramblers, let's get to rambling.  Wait a minute, who didn't throw in", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": " Mr. my friend?  Why", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " Mr. my friend?  Why", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " He don't tip?  You don't tip?  Why", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "He don't tip", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "He don't believe in it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " He don't tip?  You don't tip?  Why", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " He don't believe in it?  You don't believe in it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": " What the fuck am I doing here?  I felt funny about this job right off.  As soon as I felt it I should said", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I'm cool", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "At that point it became every man for himself.  As far as Mr. my friend or Mr. my friend are concerned, I ain't got the foggiest.  Once I got out, I never looked back", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What do I think?  I think the cops caught them, or killed 'em", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Not even a chance they punched through?  You found a hole", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You don't think it's possible, one of them got ahold of the diamonds and pulled ", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "So who's the rat this time?  Mr. my friend?  Mr. my friend?  my friend?  It's my friend's show, he set this whole thing up.  Maybe he set it up to set it up", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, you and my friend go back a long time.  I known my friend since I was a kid.  But me saying my friend definitely couldn't have done it is ridiculous.  I can say I definitely didn't do it, cause I know what I did or didn't do.  But I can't definitely say that about anybody else, 'cause I don't definitely know.  For all I know, you're the rat", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Oh, you and my friend go back a long time.  I known my friend since I was a kid.  But me saying my friend definitely couldn't have done it is ridiculous.  I can say I definitely didn't do it, cause I know what I did or didn't do.  But I can't definitely say that about anybody else, 'cause I don't definitely know.  For all I know, you're the rat", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Now you're using your head. For all we know, he's the rat", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Well, he knows a little about me", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " I told him my first name, and where I'm from", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " We had just gotten away from the cops.  He just got shot.  It was my fuckin fault he got shot.  He's a fuckin bloody mess", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": " Don't fuckin patronize me", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "You talked to Nice Guy my friend?  Why the fuck didn't you say that in the first place", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Hard", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": " What's your name", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "my friend what", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "my friend introduced us once, about five months ago", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I do.  How do I look", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "No, he ain't familiar.  He ain't one of my friend's soldiers either. He's gotta be from outta town. But my friend knows him real well", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "The way they talk to each other. You can tell they're buddies", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "What about", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "The that place", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I'll make you a bet that those same damn niggers who were showin their ass in public, when their bitches get 'em home, they chill the fuck out", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Yeah, those guys too", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Yeah, Elois. E and my friend.  We called her Lady E", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": "No.  She was from that place", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "You don't know jack shit.  I do. This rotten bastard tipped off the cops and got Mr. my friend and Mr. my friend killed", "docId": "Reservoir-Dogs.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "Dead as my friend", "qsentId": 54}]